const questionStore = {
    correctAnswers: 0,
      
    questions:[
    {
        questNmb: 1,
        problem: "In the popular book and television show 'Game of Thrones' who masterminded the plot to kill King Joffrey?",
        choices: [
            "Lord Varys",
            "Olenna Tyrell",
            "Ren√© Artois",
            "Little Mix"
        ],
        solution: "Olenna Tyrell"
    },
    
    {
       questNmb: 2,   
       problem: "What is NOT one of the colors of the rainbow?",
       choices: [
            "Red",
            "Violet",
            "Pink",
            "Indigo"
        ],
        solution: "Pink"
    },
  
    {
        questNmb: 3,   
        problem: "In the latest Star Wars movie 'The Last Jedi', who are Rey's parents?",
        choices: [
            "Han Solo and Leia Organa",
            "Some insignificant people",
            "Luke Skywalker and Mara Jade",
            "Obi-Wan Kenobi and Satine Kryze"
        ],
        solution: "Some insignificant people"
    },
      
    {
        questNmb: 4,   
        problem: "Which of these is the correct lyrics to the song 'Bohemian Rhapsody'?",
        choices: [
            "Mama, you just killed a man",
            "Sends lots of shivers down my spine",
            "Carry on, carry on",
            "Goodbye everybody, I'm not gonna go"
        ],
        solution: "Carry on, carry on"
    },
      
    {
        questNmb: 5,   
        problem: "In the anime/manga 'One Piece', who is not part of the Straw Hat crew?",
        choices: [
            "Brook",
            "Nami",
            "Ace",
            "Zoro"
        ],
        solution: "Ace"
    },
   
    {
        questNmb: 6,
        problem: "What famous food was formerly known as the Blue Ribbon Burger?",
        choices: [
            "Sliders",
            "Big Mac",
            "Whopper",
            "Hot Dogs"
        ],
        solution: "Big Mac"
    },
      
    {
        questNmb: 7,
        problem: "Visiting what food diner has become a Christmas tradition in Japan?",
        choices: [
            "KFC",
            "Ramen bar",
            "Jack in the Box",
            "Burger King"
        ],
        solution: "KFC"
    },
      
    {
        questNmb: 8,
        problem: "In the popular book series 'Harry Potter' who does Harry marry?",
        choices: [
            "Luna Lovegood",
            "Hermione Granger",
            "Ginerva Weasley",
            "Epilogue? What epilogue?"
        ],
        solution: "Ginerva Weasley"
    },
      
    {
        questNmb: 9,
        problem: "In the popular video game, 'Mario', what is not considered a power-up?",
        choices: [
            "Mushroom",
            "Block",
            "Star",
            "Flower"
        ],
        solution: "Block"
    },
      
    {
        questNmb: 10,
        problem: "What is Elias' (previous instructor for nw-cohort8) last name?",
        choices: [
            "Muse",
            "Ron",
            "Burgandy",
            "Mason"
        ],
        solution: "Mason"
    },
    ],

    response: '',
    currentQuestionIndex: 0,
}